Ahmed Mumit Mehdi Rahman

Address:
Queen's Park, London

Phone:

+44 (0) 74 7025 5640

Emails

ammrahman05@gmail.com

Personal Statement

I am a highly motivated and versatile professional with a BSc in Data Science and Analytics and a BBA in Management Information Systems, I bring a unique blend of technical and managerial expertise. My experience spans roles from End User Support Technician and CRM Database Process Optimizer at the University of Westminster to leadership positions such as Treasurer of the University's First Aid Society and Shift Manager at McDonald's. Certified in Azure Fundamentals, cybersecurity, web design, and data analysis, I am equipped with the skills to thrive in fast-paced environments.

Experiences

- Worked as End User Support Technician in Information Systems and Support department at University of Westminster from 11 October 2023 to 31 July 2024.
- Appointed as School Representative of the School of Computer Science and Engineering at University of Westminster from 30 May 2023 to 31 July 2024.
- Worked as CRM Database Process and Optimizer in Global Recruitment, Admissions, Marketing, and Communications department at University of Westminster from 03 January 2023 to 31 August 2023.
- Worked as **Student Ambassador** at **University of Westminster** from 17 August 2022 to 31 July 2024.
- Worked as **Treasurer** of **University of Westminster First Aid Society** from 24 August 2022 to 31 July 2023.
- Managed as Shift Manager at McDonald's from 16 July 2022 to 17 January 2023.
- Promoted to **Treasurer** of **Sonchalon** (A voluntary blood donors' organization of Shahjalal University of Science and Technology) from 17 February 2020 to 14 November 2021.
- Employed as an ICT Teacher at Orbit Coaching Home.
- Employed as an ICT Teacher at Uranium Coaching Centre.
- Collaborated as **Assistant General Secretary** of **Sonchalon** (A voluntary blood donors' organization of Shahjalal University of Science and Technology) from 10 March 2019 to 16 February 2020.

Educational Qualifications

- BSc (Bachelor of Science) in Data Science and Analytics, University of Westminster Graduate Year 2024
- BBA (Bachelor of Business Administration) in Management Information Systems, Shahjalal University of Science and Technology
- Higher Secondary Certificate (A Level), Scholarshome

Group: Science Grade: 4.33/5.0

• Secondary School Certificate (O Level), Moulvibazar Govt. High School

Group: Science Grade: 5.0/5.0

Certifications

- Microsoft certified Azure Fundamentals.
- "C Programming Language"- National Academy for Computer Training and Research, Bangladesh.
- "Web Design and Development"- Sheikh Kamal IT Training and Incubation Center Project, Bangladesh.
- "Introduction to Cybersecurity"- Cisco Networking Academy.
- "Practical MySQL for Data Analysis"- Udemy: Ligency Team.
- "Microsoft Excel Masterclass-2021"- Udemy: Logistic & Supply Chain World.